CLAIRE HARDMAN

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Stockholm | +46 763416772 | chardma3.github.io/hardman-dev | github.com/chardma3 | linkedin.com/in/claire-hardman-862a558b

SKILLS

Technical skills

JavaScript ES6 | Python
HTML | CSS
Bootstrap | React
Django | Flask
Mongo DB | SQL

Stripe | AWS | Heroku
| Github | Slack

Transferable skills

Highly organised
Attention to detail
Love learning
Solution Oriented
Excellent verbal &
written skills
Self-starter
Leadership skills
Efficient
Positive & Social
Creative-thinker

Other Programs

Photoshop |
Lightroom | Capture
One | Final Cut Pro X |
Adobe Premiere | Avid
| Ableton | Logic Pro X

Languages

English (Native)
Swedish (Fluent)
Spanish (Beginner)

Key Achievements

Played Stadium Events
Won 2 DJ competitions
Won Years Best
Director at Film and TV
School

Full-Stack Development graduate from Code Institute 2021. Highly creative and have experience of bringing projects from inception to completion in several fields such as video editing, photography and music. These industries require split second decisions in high pressure environments, decisive communication, a cool head and attention to detail. I have strong communication skills in a multi-international environment. Am ready to take the next step in my life and bring all of these qualities to my career in tech. Would love to be given the opportunity work at Ericsson and to grow with one of the world's most inspiring and innovative companies and develop technologies that can improve and impact the world we live in. Recently undertook a course in Ericssons own Erlang to prepare me for the role. References can be provided on request.

EDUCATION

Code Institute

University Credit-Rated Diploma in Software Dev (2021)

Milestone Project 4: Hardman Photo

HTML | CSS | Javascript | Python | Django | Bootstrap | AWS | Heroku | Git | Stripe | SQL A fully functioning E-commerce store allowing users to create an account and order pictures delivered to a given address using Stripe payment service.

Milestone Project 3: Best Bars

HTML | CSS | Javascript | Python | Bootstrap | MongoDB | Heroku | Git | Flask A Bar review website allowing users to create an account and publish, edit and delete reviews built with micro -framework Flask and python.

Milestone Project 2: Summer Memories

HTML | CSS | Javascript

A summer themed flip-card memory game built with object -oriented programming in JavaScript including sound fx and a moving gradient background.

Milestone Project 1: Capino M/S

HTML | CSS | Bootstrap

A one page scrolling web application for a yacht entertainment service with a contact form for potential clients to contact the site owner.

Armidale Film & TV School (TAFE, NSW, AUS)

Diploma in Screen with Distinction (2005)

Direction | Video editing | Cinematography | Production | Sound Design

WORK EXPERIENCE

Composer and DJ

Claire Hardman Music (2010-present)

Consultative collaboration with clients before and during events to cater to a specific demographic

Photographer/videographer

Hardman Photo (2011-present)

Freelance photography and editing projects for private individuals and companies

Photographers Assistant

Photographer Pelle Lundberg AB (2016-2019)

Managing technical and client operations in a busy commercial environment

Studio Assistant

H&M Photo Studios (2018)

Part time studio operations role focussed on technical equipment and ensuring production activities ran smoothly